Guide to the AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council records, 1944-2000; 1970-2000; 0450-017; 44.48 cubic ft. 44 boxes
  - CONVENTIONS AND CONFERENCE RECORDS, SERIES IV (Box-folder 2/19-6/3; 43/1-3, 44)
    - Legislative Conferences, 1989-1999; Subseries A (Box-folder 2/19-30; 43/1-3, 44)
      - Packet, 1993 (Box-folder 2/26)
      - Correspondence and Agenda, 1989 (Box-folder 2/27)
      - Lobbying Conference, 1989 (Box-folder 2/28)
      - Planning and Correspondence, 1989 (Box-folder 2/29)
      - Labor Strategies Conference (Box-folder 2/30)
      - Central Labor Council Conference, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 43/1-2)
      - WSLC Legislative Conference, 1997 (Box-folder 43/3)
      - "Labor Looks" reports on the Washington State Legislature, 1959-1977 (Box-folder 44)
    - Committee on Political Education Conventions, 1984-2006; Subseries B (Box-folder 2/31-2/33)
      - Participant Packet: Committee on Political Education Convention, 2006 (Box-folder 2/31)
      - Catering Order and Participants' Packet Materials, 1992 (Box-folder 2/32)
      - Statewide Convention, 1984 (Box-folder 2/33)
    - Ergonomics Conference, 1999; Subseries C (Box-folder 2/34)
      - Ergonomics Conference Registration, 1999 (Box-folder 2/34)
    - Transportation Conference, 1999; Subseries D (Box-folder 2/35)
      - Transportation Conference Sign-in and Materials, 1999 (Box-folder 2/35)
    - Constitutional Conventions, 1972-1998; Subseries E (Box-folder 3/1-6/3; 41/1-28)
      - Speak Out! Speakers and Artists, 1996- 1998 (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Committee Members, 1998 (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Correspondence, 1998 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Logistics and Planning, 1998 (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Original Resolutions, 1998 (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Typed Resolutions, 1998 (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Schedules, 1998 (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Correspondence, 1997 (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Resolutions, 1997 (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Schedules, 1997 (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Committees, 1997 (Box-folder 3/11)
      - Logistics and Planning, 1997 (Box-folder 3/12)
      - Final Resolutions, 1997 (Box-folder 3/13)
      - Rick Bender File, 1996 (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Correspondence, 1996 (Box-folder 3/15)
      - Committee Action Sheets, 1996 (Box-folder 3/16)
      - Committees, 1996 (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Final Resolutions, 1996 (Box-folder 3/18)
      - Schedules, 1996 (Box-folder 3/19)
      - Committees, 1995 (Box-folder 3/20)
      - Resolutions, 1995 (Box-folder 3/21)
      - Planning and Logistics, 1995 (Box-folder 3/22)
      - Logistics and Planning, 1992- 1994 (Box-folder 3/23)
      - Schedules, Proceedings, Committees, and Correspondence (1 of 2), 1994 (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Schedules, Proceedings, Committees, and Correspondence (2 of 2), 1994 (Box-folder 3/25)
      - Resolutions, 1994 (Box-folder 3/26)
      - Resolutions, 1993 (Box-folder 3/27)
      - Packet, 1993 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Resolution Number 3 Committee: Changing the Executive Board, 1992 (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Convention Planning and Correspondence (1 of 3), 1993 (Box-folder 4/3)
      - Convention Planning and Correspondence (2 of 3), 1993 (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Convention Planning and Correspondence (3 of 3), 1993 (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Official Convention Call, 1992 (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Partial Proceedings and Packet Materials, 1992 (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Guest List, 1992 (Box-folder 4/8)
      - Convention Business, 1992 (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Resolutions, 1992 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Convention Call and Packet Materials, 1991 (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Committees, 1991 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Guest List, 1991 (Box-folder 4/13)
      - Correspondence, 1991 (Box-folder 4/14)
      - Convention Call, Packet Materials, and Proposed Rules of Order, 1990 (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Resolutions, 1990 (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Summary Proceedings, 1990 (Box-folder 4/17)
      - Agenda, 1989 (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Convention Call and Packet Materials, 1989 (Box-folder 4/19)
      - Planning Materials and Proposed Rules of Order, 1989 (Box-folder 4/20)
      - Convention Call and Correspondence, 1989 (Box-folder 4/21)
      - Packet Materials, 1988 (Box-folder 4/22)
      - Planning Materials and Proposed Rules of Order, 1988 (Box-folder 4/23)
      - Planning and Correspondence, 1987 (Box-folder 4/24)
      - Resolutions, 1987 (Box-folder 4/25)
      - Packet materials, 1986 (Box-folder 41/1)
      - Correspondence, 1986 (Box-folder 41/2)
      - Committees (part 1 of 2), 1986 (Box-folder 41/3)
      - Committees (part 2 of 2), 1986 (Box-folder 41/4)
      - Planning and correspondence, 1986 (Box-folder 41/5-6)
      - Planning and correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 41/7)
      - Credentials, 1986 (Box-folder 41/8-9)
      - Evaluation forms, 1986 (Box-folder 41/10)
      - Packet materials, 1985 (Box-folder 41/11)
      - Planning and correspondence, 1985 (Box-folder 41/12-13)
      - Registration and invitations, 1985 (Box-folder 41/14)
      - Guests, 1985 (Box-folder 41/15)
      - Delegate lists, 1985 (Box-folder 41/16)
      - Committees, 1985 (Box-folder 41/16)
      - Resolutions, 1985 (Box-folder 41/17)
      - Committee reports on resolutions, 1985 (Box-folder 41/18)
      - Legislative tabloid, 1985 (Box-folder 41/19)
      - Registration and agenda, 1984 (Box-folder 41/20)
      - Guests, 1984 (Box-folder 41/21)
      - Committees, 1984 (Box-folder 41/22)
      - Ad hoc Committee on Affiliation, 1984 (Box-folder 41/23)
      - Resolutions, 1984 (Box-folder 41/24)
      - Daily proceedings, 1984 (Box-folder 41/25)
      - News articles and editorials, 1984 (Box-folder 41/26)
      - Memorial service, 1984 (Box-folder 41/27)
      - Convention notes, 1984 (Box-folder 41/28)
      - Resolutions, 1984 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Summary Proceedings, 1984 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Resolutions and Resolution Control Sheet, 1984 (Box-folder 5/4)
      - Planning Materials, 1984 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Union Label and Trades Council, 1985 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Committee Officers and Appointments, 1984 (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Program, Speakers and Schedule, 1984 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Agreements, Arrangements and Contracts, 1984 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Registration and Hotel Reservations, 1984 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - Workshops, Meetings and Ideas, 1984 (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Proceedings Bids, 1982 (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Summary Proceedings, 1982 (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Committees and Rules, 1982 (Box-folder 5/14)
      - Administration and Convention Call, 1982 (Box-folder 5/15)
      - Correspondence, 1987 (Box-folder 5/16)
      - Convention packet, 1987 (Box-folder 5/17)
      - Correspondence and schedules - Part 1, 1988 (Box-folder 5/18)
      - Correspondence and schedules - Part 2, 1988 (Box-folder 5/19)
      - Guest invitations, 1988 (Box-folder 5/20)
      - Correspondence and schedules, 1989 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - Correspondence and schedules, 1990 (Box-folder 5/22)
      - Correspondence and schedules - Part 1, 1991 (Box-folder 5/23)
      - Correspondence and schedules - Part 2, 1991 (Box-folder 5/24)
      - Convention Resolutions (Originals): Resolutions 1-49, 1972 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Convention Resolutions (Originals): Resolutions 50- 134, 1972 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - Resolutions and Section Officials, 1972 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1944-1990; Subseries F (Box-folder 44)
      - Washington State Federation of Labor annual convention proceedings, 1944-1968 (Box-folder 44)
      - Washington State Labor Council, AFL-CIO annual convention proceedings, 1969-1990 (Box-folder 44)
  - CONVENTION COMMITTEE RECORDS, 1972-1993; SERIES V (Box-folder 6/4-7/9)
    - Original Convention Resolutions by the Resolutions Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Original Convention Resolutions by the Label & Unfair Lists Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Parliamentarian and Sergeants-at-arms Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Report of Officers Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Committee on Political Education, 1973 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Rules & Order of Business Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - Grievances Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - Industrial Safety Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 6/11)
    - Original Convention Resolutions by the Constitution Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 6/12)
    - Original Convention Resolutions by the Legislative Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 6/13)
    - Original Convention Resolutions by the Statewide Committee on Political Education, 1972 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - Constitution and Bylaws Committee: Constitution Review, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Convention Committees (1 of 3), 1991- 1993 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Convention Committees (2 of 3), 1991-1993 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Convention Committees (3 of 3), 1991-1993 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Convention Committees, 1990 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - Convention Committees, 1989 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Convention Committees, 1988 (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Convention Committees, 1987 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - Committee Participation, 1987 (Box-folder 7/9)
  - COMMITTEE ON POLITICAL EDUCATION RECORDS, SERIES VI (Box-folder 7/10-7/26)
    - Campaigns, 1987- 1996; Subseries A (Box-folder 7/10-7/13)
      - COPE, 1987 (Box-folder 7/10)
      - COPE, 1988 (Box-folder 7/11)
      - COPE, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 7/12)
      - COPE, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - Committee on Political Education Endorsing Conventions, 1984-1997; Subseries B (Box-folder 7/14-7/21)
      - COPE endorsements, 1987- 1988 (Box-folder 7/14)
      - COPE Convention May 1988 (Box-folder 7/15)
      - COPE Convention September 1988 (Box-folder 7/16)
      - COPE Convention packet, 1990 (Box-folder 7/17)
      - COPE Convention, 1984 (Box-folder 7/18)
      - COPE Convention, 1992 (Box-folder 7/19)
      - COPE endorsements, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 7/20)
      - COPE endorsements, 1997 (Box-folder 7/21)
    - Financial Records, 1993- 1996; Subseries C (Box-folder 7/22-7/26)
      - 1994 Budget, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 7/22)
      - 1995 Budget (Box-folder 7/23)
      - 1996 Budget (Box-folder 7/24)
      - 1996 Expenditures - Part 1 (Box-folder 7/25)
      - 1996 Expenditures - Part 2 (Box-folder 7/26)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, SERIES VII (Box-folder 8/1-11/2; 42/1-3)
    - Affiliate Mailings by Year, 1987-2014; Subseries A (Box-folder 8/1-7, 23/2)
      - Affiliates, 1987 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Affiliates, 1988 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Affiliates, 1989 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Affiliates, 1990 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - New affiliate letters, 1996- 1998 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Affiliates, 2006 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Affiliates, 2007 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Affiliates, 2014 (Box-folder 23/2)
    - General Correspondence, 1974-2000; Subseries B (Box-folder 8/9-10/6; 42/1-3)
      - AFL-CIO correspondence / newspapers, 1994 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - AFL-CIO publications, 1993 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - AFL-CIO Regional meeting, 1989 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - A. Phillip Randolph Institute, 1994 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Board of Industrial Insurance Appeals, 1993 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Building and Construction Trades Council, 1993 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Campaign contributions, 1993 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Campaign finance: draft training materials, 1993 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Church-Labor Community Forum, 1993 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Coalition for a Livable Washington, 1993 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1974- 1982 (Box-folder 8/20)
      - Columbia River Alliance, 1994 (Box-folder 8/21)
      - Comparative Labor History Series, 1992- 1993 (Box-folder 8/22)
      - Convention, 1987 (Box-folder 8/23)
      - Education, Training and Apprenticeship Committee, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 8/24)
      - Employment and Unemployment Committee, 1987 (Box-folder 8/25)
      - Environmental and Economic Benefit Council, 1994 (Box-folder 8/26)
      - ERISA, 1993 (Box-folder 8/27)
      - Executive Board, 1988 (Box-folder 8/28)
      - Executive Board make- up, 1992 (Box-folder 8/29)
      - General, 1987 (Box-folder 8/30)
      - General, 1988 (Box-folder 8/31)
      - General, 1993 (Box-folder 8/32)
      - Multiple recipient mailings - Part 1, 1982 (Box-folder 8/33)
      - Multiple recipient mailings - Part 2, 1982 (Box-folder 8/34)
      - Multiple recipient mailings - Part 1, 1983 (Box-folder 8/35)
      - Multiple recipient mailings - Part 2, 1984 (Box-folder 8/36)
      - Governor's Council on School to Work Transition, 1994 (Box-folder 8/37)
      - Group Health Cooperative, 1993 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Hatch Act reform, 1989 (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Health care reform, 1993 (Box-folder 9/3)
      - International trade, 1993 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Interoffice memos, 1987 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Legislation, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Legislative Update, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Legislative Update, 1989 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Lifestyle discrimination, 1992 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Mail ballots on issues, 1989 (Box-folder 42/1)
      - Mail ballots on issues, 1990 (Box-folder 42/2)
      - Mail ballots on issues, 1991 (Box-folder 42/3)
      - Membership warehouse clubs, 1991 (Box-folder 9/10)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement, 1993 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - News releases, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 9/12)
      - Northwest Alternatives, 1992 (Box-folder 9/13)
      - Officers and staff retreat, 1993 (Box-folder 9/14)
      - Outstanding Legislator Award, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 9/15)
      - Pacific Coast Economic Recovery Plan, 1993 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - Press conferences, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 9/17)
      - Progressive Coalition, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 9/18)
      - Project Help, 1993 (Box-folder 9/19)
      - Public Employee Committee, 1988 (Box-folder 9/20)
      - Rainbow Coalition, 1993 (Box-folder 9/21)
      - Responsible contractor policy, 1993 (Box-folder 9/22)
      - Seattle Commons, 1994 (Box-folder 9/23)
      - Seattle Fire Fighters Union Local 27, 1994 (Box-folder 9/24)
      - Solidarnosc, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 9/25)
      - State AFL-CIO position on abortion, 1990 (Box-folder 9/26)
      - State boards and commissions, 1994 (Box-folder 9/27)
      - Support Group for Prevailing Wage, 1990 (Box-folder 9/28)
      - Task Force for the Prevention of Long-term Disability, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 9/29)
      - TESC Labor Center Advisory Committee, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 9/30)
      - Toycott - Part 1, 1991- 1994 (Box-folder 9/31)
      - Toycott - Part 2, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 9/32)
      - Trade mission to Poland, 1995 (Box-folder 9/33)
      - Unemployment insurance, 1976 (Box-folder 9/34)
      - Unemployment insurance reform, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 9/35)
      - Union survey projects, 1985- 1987 (Box-folder 9/36)
      - United Labor Lobby minutes, 1987 (Box-folder 9/37)
      - United Labor Lobby, 1993 (Box-folder 9/38)
      - United Labor Lobby, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 9/39)
      - United Labor Lobby hotline messages, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 9/40)
      - Washington Citizen Action, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 9/41)
      - Washington Transportation Policy Institute, 1993 (Box-folder 9/42)
      - White House Forest Conference, 1993 (Box-folder 9/43)
      - WISHA Monitoring/Industrial Insurance Committee, 1988 (Box-folder 9/44)
      - WISHA Monitoring Committee, 1994 (Box-folder 9/45)
      - Women and minors, 1972- 1982 (Box-folder 9/46)
      - Women's Committee, 1988 (Box-folder 10/1)
      - Workforce training, 1993- 1984 (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Workers' Compensation Advisory Committee, 1993 (Box-folder 10/3)
      - WSLC Reports, 1988 (Box-folder 10/4)
      - WSLC Reports, 1987 (Box-folder 10/5)
      - WSLC Reports, 1988 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Bender Correspondence, 1993- 1995; Subseries C (Box-folder 10/7-11/2)
      - Incoming, 1993 (Box-folder 10/7)
      - Outgoing 1st Quarter 1993 (Box-folder 10/8)
      - Outgoing 2nd Quarter 1993 - Part 1 (Box-folder 10/9)
      - Outgoing 2nd Quarter 1993 - Part 2 (Box-folder 10/10)
      - Outgoing 3rd Quarter 1993 (Box-folder 10/11)
      - Outgoing 4th Quarter 1993 (Box-folder 10/12)
      - Incoming January-June 1994 (Box-folder 10/13)
      - Incoming July-December 1994 (Box-folder 10/14)
      - Outgoing 1st Quarter 1994 (Box-folder 10/15)
      - Outgoing 2nd Quarter 1994 - Part 1 (Box-folder 10/16)
      - Outgoing 2nd Quarter 1994 - Part 2 (Box-folder 10/17)
      - Outgoing 3rd Quarter 1994 (Box-folder 10/18)
      - Outgoing 4th Quarter 1994 (Box-folder 10/19)
      - Incoming January-June 1995 (Box-folder 10/20)
      - Incoming July-December 1995 (Box-folder 10/21)
      - Outgoing 1st Quarter 1995 (Box-folder 10/22)
      - Outgoing 2nd Quarter 1995 (Box-folder 10/23)
      - Outgoing 3rd Quarter 1995 (Box-folder 11/1)
      - Outgoing 4th Quarter 1995 (Box-folder 11/2)
  - EXECUTIVE BOARD RECORDS, SERIES VII (Box-folder 11/3-17/30)
    - Meetings, 1973-1983; Subseries A (Box-folder 11/3)
      - Agendas, 1973- 1983 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Minutes and Meeting Materials, 1969- 1993; Subseries B (Box-folder 11/4-14/4)
      - Minutes, 1969 (Box-folder 11/4)
      - Minutes, 1970 (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Minutes, 1971 (Box-folder 11/6)
      - Minutes, 1972 (Box-folder 11/7)
      - Minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 11/8)
      - Minutes, 1974 (Box-folder 11/9)
      - Minutes, 1975 (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Minutes, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 11/11)
      - Meeting materials January 24, 1984 (Box-folder 11/12)
      - Meeting materials April 20, 1984 (Box-folder 11/13)
      - Meeting materials July 6, 1984 (Box-folder 11/14)
      - Meeting materials 8/24/1984 (Box-folder 11/15)
      - Meeting materials 10/6/1984 (Box-folder 11/16)
      - Meeting materials 11/29/1984 (Box-folder 11/17)
      - Meeting materials 12/27/1984 (Box-folder 11/18)
      - Meeting materials 1/18/1985 (Box-folder 11/19)
      - Meeting materials 5/3/1985 (Box-folder 11/20)
      - Meeting materials 8/9/1985 (Box-folder 11/21)
      - Meeting materials 9/19/1985 (Box-folder 11/22)
      - Meeting materials 11/15/1985 (Box-folder 11/23)
      - Meeting materials 12/20/1985 (Box-folder 11/24)
      - Meeting materials 1/18/1986 (Box-folder 12/1)
      - Meeting materials 4/17/1986 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Meeting materials 6/6/1986 (Box-folder 12/3)
      - Meeting materials 8/21/1986 (Box-folder 12/4)
      - Meeting materials 10/3/1986 (Box-folder 12/5)
      - Meeting materials 12/11/1986 (Box-folder 12/6)
      - Meeting materials 2/26/1987 (Box-folder 12/7)
      - Meeting materials 4/6/1987 (Box-folder 12/8)
      - Meeting materials 5/15/1987 (Box-folder 12/9)
      - Meeting materials 6/25/1987 (Box-folder 12/10)
      - Meeting materials 7/17/1987 (Box-folder 12/11)
      - Meeting materials 8/21/1987 (Box-folder 12/12)
      - Meeting materials 9/17/1987 (Box-folder 12/13)
      - Meeting materials 12/11/1987 (Box-folder 12/14)
      - Meeting materials 1/8/1988 (Box-folder 12/15)
      - Meeting materials 4/15/1988 (Box-folder 12/16)
      - Meeting materials 5/20/1988 (Box-folder 12/17)
      - Meeting materials 7/8/1988 (Box-folder 12/18)
      - Meeting materials 8/19/1988 (Box-folder 12/19)
      - Meeting materials 9/23/1988 (Box-folder 12/20)
      - Meeting materials 12/9/1988 (Box-folder 12/21)
      - Meeting materials 3/21/1989 (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Meeting materials 5/12/1989 (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Meeting materials 7/28/1989 (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Meeting materials 9/20/1989 (Box-folder 13/4)
      - Meeting materials 10/26/1989 (Box-folder 13/5)
      - Meeting materials 1/12/1990 (Box-folder 13/6)
      - Meeting materials 4/27/1990 (Box-folder 13/7)
      - Meeting materials 5/18/1990 (Box-folder 13/8)
      - Meeting materials 7/25/1990 (Box-folder 13/9)
      - Meeting materials 8/24/1990 (Box-folder 13/10)
      - Meeting materials 9/22/1990 (Box-folder 13/11)
      - Meeting materials 12/7/1990 (Box-folder 13/12)
      - Meeting materials 3/18/1991 (Box-folder 13/13)
      - Meeting materials 4/5/1991 (Box-folder 13/14)
      - Meeting materials 6/7/1991 (Box-folder 13/15)
      - Meeting materials 7/22/1991 (Box-folder 13/16)
      - Meeting materials 9/18/1991 (Box-folder 13/17)
      - Meeting materials 12/13/1991 (Box-folder 13/18)
      - Meeting materials 1/10/1992 (Box-folder 13/19)
      - Meeting materials 5/15/1992 (Box-folder 13/20)
      - Meeting materials 7/24/1992 (Box-folder 13/21)
      - Meeting materials 8/22/1992 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Meeting materials 11/20/1992 (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Meeting materials 1/15/1993 (Box-folder 14/3)
      - Meeting materials 2/19/1993 (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Reading Files: Outgoing, 1982-1991; Subseries C (Box-folder 14/5-14/37; 15/1-15/46; 16/1-16/22)
    - Reading Files: Incoming, 1987-1999; Subseries D (Box-folder 16/23-16/55; 17/1-17/30)
  - DIRECTORIES, 1992-1999; SERIES IX
    - Directory of Organizations, 1992- 1993 (Box-folder 17/31)
    - Directory of Organizations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 17/32)
    - Directory of Organizations, 1997- 1998 (Box-folder 17/33)
    - Directory of Organizations, 1999 (Box-folder 17/34)
  - PENSION PLAN RECORDS, 1959-1988; SERIES X (Box-folder 17/35-18/2; 42/4-7)
    - Bankers Life Company: Group Contract GA 3209, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 17/35)
    - Bankers Life Company: Group Contract GA 3209 amendment no. 2, 1976 (Box-folder 17/36)
    - Bankers Life Company: Group Contract GA 3209 amendment no. 3, 1978 (Box-folder 17/37)
    - Bankers Life Company: Group Contract GA 3209, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 17/38)
    - Bankers Life Company: Group Contract GA 3209 restated Jan 1 1976 (Box-folder 17/39)
    - Bankers Life Company: General correspondence and CLU reports, 1959-1974 (Box-folder 17/40)
    - Bankers Life Company: Correspondence with IRS and related reports, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 17/41)
    - D-1S Report, 1973- 1975 (Box-folder 17/42)
    - Bankers Life Company: Group Contract GA 3209 federal tax status, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 17/43)
    - Officers and staff pension proposals and working papers, 1975 (Box-folder 17/44)
    - Group pension contracts, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 42/4)
    - Group pension contracts, 1988 (Box-folder 42/5)
    - Defined benefit plan restated January 1, 1984 (Box-folder 42/6)
    - Pension plan reports and correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 42/7)
    - Western States Pension Fund Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 17/45)
    - Federal pension legislation -- Part 1, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 18/1)
    - Federal pension legislation -- Part 2, 1974- 1978 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - PERSONNEL ADMINISTRATION RECORDS, 1954- 1992; SERIES XI (Box-folder 18/3-18/23)
    - Policy regarding staff seeking public office or position in affiliates, 1969-1985 (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Personnel memos, 1974- 1980 (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Memo instructions to staff, 1967-1980 (Box-folder 18/5)
    - Staff reductions, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 18/6)
    - Staff job descriptions and reports, 1971- 1982 (Box-folder 18/7)
    - Affiliation Program coordinator, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Project Help director -- Part 1, 1990 (Box-folder 18/9)
    - Project Help director -- Part 2, 1990 (Box-folder 18/10)
    - Project Help director: finalists, 1990 (Box-folder 18/11)
    - Employees' health and welfare funds, 1954-1980 (Box-folder 18/12)
    - Standard Insurance Company: group insurance, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 18/13)
    - Policy re staff salaries and benefits, 1969- 1975 (Box-folder 18/14)
    - Welfare and Pension Administrative Service Inc. reimbursement of salary expense, 1970- 1980 (Box-folder 18/15)
    - Life Insurance Company of North America, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 18/16)